//creating an array and passing the number

let questions=[
    {
        numb:1,
        question:" In the Josephus problem, if there are 10 people standing in a circle and every 3rd person is eliminated, what is the position of the last remaining person??",
        answer:"4",
        options:[
            "5",
            "4",
            "7",
            "6"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question:"In the Tower of Hanoi puzzle, what is the minimum number of moves required to solve a 4-disk problem?",
        answer:"15",
        options:[
            "17",
            "15",
            "13",
            "12"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:3,
        question:"Which mathematical technique is used to approximate solutions to problems by adding small perturbations to known solutions?",
        answer:"Perturbation Method",
        options:[
            "Josephus Method",
            "Tower of Hanoi Method",
            "Perturbation Method",
            "Floor & Ceiling"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:4,
        question:"In the Josephus problem, if there are 15 people standing in a circle and every 4th person is eliminated, what is the position of the last remaining person?",
        answer:"3",
        options:[
            "3",
            "4",
            "23",
            "6"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question:"If x = 5.7, what is the floor and ceiling of x?",
        answer:"5,6",
        options:[
            "4,5",
            "5,6",
            "7,8",
            "9,11"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question:"Euler's Theorem: State Euler's theorem and explain its significance in number theory.",
        answer:"Euler's theorem states that a^φ(n) ≡ 1 (mod n) for any integer a and positive integer n.",
        options:[
            "Euler's theorem states that a^φ(n) ≡ 1 (mod n) for any integer a and positive integer n.",
            "Euler's theorem states that a^φ(n) ≡ 0 (mod n) for any integer a and positive integer n.",
            "Euler's theorem states that a^φ(n) ≡ a (mod n) for any integer a and positive integer n.",
            "Euler's theorem states that a^φ(n) ≡ -a (mod n) for any integer a and positive integer n."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question:"Given four positive integers a, b, c, and d, prove that GCD(a, b) * GCD(c, d) = GCD(AC, BD), where AC denotes the product of a and c, and BD denotes the product of b and d.",
        answer:"GCD(a, b) * GCD(c, d) = GCD(AC, BD)",
        options:[
            "GCD(a, c) * GCD(b, d) = GCD(AC, BD)",
            "GCD(a, b) * GCD(c, d) = GCD(AC, BD)",
            "GCD(a, b) * GCD(c, d) = GCD(A + B, C + D)",
            "GCD(a, c) * GCD(b, d) = GCD(A + B, C + D)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question:" Prove that the sum of any three consecutive positive odd integers is always divisible by 3.",
        answer:"True",
        options:[
            "False",
            "Only for the first three odd integers",
            "True",
            "Only for the last three odd integers"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question:"Given two positive integers a and b, prove that GCD(a, b) * LCM(a, b) = a * b.",
        answer:"GCD(a, b) * LCM(a, b) = a * b",
        options:[
            "GCD(a, b) * GCD(c, d) = GCD(A + B, C + D)",
            "GCD(a, b) * LCM(a, b) = a * b",
            "GCD(a, c) * GCD(b, d) = GCD(AC, BD)",
            "GCD(a, c) * GCD(b, d) = GCD(A + B, C + D)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question:"Josephus Method: In the Josephus problem with 30 people sitting in a circle, every 7th person is eliminated. Determine the position of the last survivor standing.",
        answer:"16",
        options:[
            "8",
            "12",
            "16",
            "18"
        ]
    }

]